(Unclear) Maybe it's the last day we see each other.
It's kind of an on-line shop where it's possible to pick a child based on age, gender...
Back to that moment I couldn't imagine it was going to be so many kids
– Have you adopted us to earn some extra (money subsidies by government)?
– Sure, of course, no doubts! (Sarcasm)
During the first period he used to cry at night
Orphanage staff works against adoption...
He can have hysterics, attacks...
The task was given: orphanages should be eliminated
No need to bring any gift
Dima Yakovlev's law was a response to Magnitski Act
They don't live as normal people because politicians have spat on them
By the moment we has sorted everything out, the ban was applied